Guide to the Yale School of Drama Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1975-1989; Accession 1990-A-032
  - Xerox, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Yale Alumni: California, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Director's Resumes, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Director's Guild of Great Britain, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - E, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 125 - 127)
  - Educational Center for the Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - F, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 130 - 132)
  - Festival of Pan-African Arts and Culture, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Fireside Entertainment, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - First New York International Festival of the Arts, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Fischer Company, Sy, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Fountain Square Fools, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - 42nd Street Non-Profit Theatre, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Urban Development (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - G, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 141 - 143)
  - General Manager Applicants, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Golden Plate Awards, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Guggenheim Fellowship, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - H, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 148 - 150)
  - Phoenix Theatre (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - Hartford Stage, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Hartman Theatre, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Hayes Award, Helen, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Hunter College, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - I, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 159 - 161)
  - Illuminating Engineering Society, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 162)
  - Independent Committee on Arts Policy John Booth, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Independent Committee on Arts Policy, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 164)
  - Institute of International Education, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 165)
  - International Theatre Institution, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 166 - 168)
  - J, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 169 - 171)
  - Johnson, Jan: The Blacks, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 172)
  - K, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 175 - 176)
  - K, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - L, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 184 - 186)
  - Labor Institute for Human Resource, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - La Jolla Playhouse, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - League of Professional Theatre Training Programs, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - League Auditions, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - League of Resident Theatres, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Lincoln Center, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Literary Managers and Dramaturgs of America, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 194)
  - Long Wharf Theatre, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - Lubimov: materials, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 196)
  - Lubimov, Yuri, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - Lubimov: Visa Preparation, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - M, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 199 - 201)
  - Martin Luther King Scholarship, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 202)
  - Martin Luther King Concert Steering Committee (Emma Ruff Co-Chair), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 203)
  - McDonald Literary Awards, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 204)
  - Minnesota Playwright Lab, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 207)
  - Mumbo Jumbo Film Society, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 209)
  - Museum of American Theatre, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 210)
  - N, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 211 - 213)
  - National Arts Week, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 214)
  - National Council on the Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 215)
  - National Public Television, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 216)
  - National Theatre, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 217)
  - National Theatre Conference, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 218)
  - National Theatre World Fellowship Conference, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 219)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Awards -- Beverly Hills, Hollywood, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 220 - 221)
  - National Black Arts Festival, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 222)
  - National Council, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 223 - 224)
  - National Endowment for the Arts: Frank Silvera Workshop, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 225)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Theatre Program, E. Martenson, Director, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 226)
  - New Haven Green, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 227)
  - New Haven Festival, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 228)
  - New York Theatre Trust, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 229)
  - New Drama Forum Association, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 230)
  - New Dramatists, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 231)
  - New England Theatre Conference, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 232)
  - New Federal Theatre: Woodie King Jr., 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 233)
  - New Haven Artists' Theatre, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 234 - 235)
  - O, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 236 - 238)
  - O'Neill
    - National Playwrights Conference Contact Sheet, 1975-1984 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Duchess Visit, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Development, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Benefit, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Institute for American Directors: Waterford, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Executive Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - International Playwrights Institute, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Institute of Professional Puppetry Arts, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - National Playwrights Conference, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Lortel gift, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Monte Cristo Cottage, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - National Playwrights Conference: External Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - National Playwrights Conference History, 1977-1984 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - NPC Staff Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - National Theatre Institute, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 255)
  - Oxford University Dramat, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 258)
  - P, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 259 - 261)
  - Philadelphia Young Playwrights, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 262)
  - Princeton, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 263)
  - Public Broadcasting Service (Box 5)
    - 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 264 - 266)
    - Greenbrier, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Negro Ensemble Company Project, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - Pilot TV Project: Image of the Black in Western Imagination
      - 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 269)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 270)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 271)
      - 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 272)
  - Program on Information Resources Policies, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 273)
  - Q, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 274 - 275)
  - R, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 276 - 278)
  - Rattner, Bonnie: Philip Hayes Dean Project, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 279)
  - Real Art Ways, undated (Box 6, Folder 280)
  - Richardson, Maxine: Autumn Beaver, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - Rockefeller: Playwrights Nominating Committee, 1980-1987 (Box 6, Folder 282 - 283)
  - Rockefeller, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 284)
  - Rollins College, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 286)
  - S, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 287 - 290)
  - SSDC, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 291)
  - Southern Film Collection, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 293)
  - Stage Manager Applicants, undated (Box 6, Folder 295)
  - Schomberg Collection, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 297)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 299)
  - Shubert Theatre, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 300)
  - Simon and Kumen, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 302)
  - Studio Museum in Harlem, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 303)
  - T, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 304 - 306)
  - Discussions with Artistic Directors, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 307)
  - Theatre Communications Group
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - Board of Directors, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - "Artist Bulletin", 1984 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - Board Meeting, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 315)
  - Temporary Help Resumes, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 317)
  - Theatre Fountainhead, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 318)
  - Thieves Theatre, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 319)
  - Tony Awards, 1983-1988 (Box 7, Folder 320)
  - Torch of Hope: Barbara Barondess, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 321)
  - U, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 322 - 324)
  - United States Information Agency, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 325)
  - V, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 326 - 328)
  - W, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 329 - 331)
  - WNET Channel 13, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 332)
  - Wilson, A. meeting, 1983-1988 (Box 7, Folder 334)
  - X, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 335)
  - Y, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 336)
  - X - Y, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 337)
  - Y, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 338)
  - Young, Glenn Applause Books: National Playwrights Conference, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 339)
  - Young Heritage House, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 340)
  - Z, 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 341 - 343)
  - Correspondence: Lloyd Richards, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 344)
  - Commencement, 1980-1987 (Box 8, Folder 345 - 351)
  - Telegrams Sent, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 352)
  - Accident Reports, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 353)
  - Business Manager, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 354)
  - Dramaturg Applicants: Yale, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 355)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre: Dramaturg Staff, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 356)
  - Dramaturg Staff, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 357)
  - Literary Managers, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 358)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre: Managing Director, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 359)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre: Press Office, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 360)
  - Press: Graphics, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 361)
  - YRT Casting: Simon and Kumin, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 362)
  - Sound Recording, 1984-1989 (Box 8, Folder 363)
  - Rep: Understudy Policy, undated (Box 8, Folder 364)
  - Buzz Ward: General Manager, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 365)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre: Yale Rep "News", 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 366)
  - The Alchemist YRT #3, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 367 - 368)
  - Master Harold, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 369)
  - Melons, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 370)
  - The Miser, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 371)
  - A Place with the Pigs: Spoletto Festival: Summer, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 372)
  - Sarcophagus, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 373)
  - The Suicide, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 374)
  - Walk in the Woods: La Jolla Playhouse Summer, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 375)
  - Warrior Ant, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 376)
  - Winterfest, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 377)
  - Lloyd Richards: Correspondence and Miscellaneous Information, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 378)
  - TCG letter for Memorial Service, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 379)
  - Ed Cole Memorial Service, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 380)
  - Lloyd Richards: Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 381)
  - Await Response, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 382)
  - Waiting for Replies, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 383)
  - Lloyd Richards: Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 384)
  - Esslin Reception, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 385)
  - Columbia Luncheon, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 386)
  - Audrey Wood Theatre, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 387)
  - Thursday, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 388)
  - Sidney Baker Meeting, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 389)
  - Lloyd Richards: Misc. Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 390)
  - Theatre Communications Group, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 391)
  - Diagnostic Meeting, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 392)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 393)
  - Annual Reports, 1976-1987 (Box 8, Folder 394 - 401)
  - Budget Plan
    - 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - Explanatory Notes, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - Endowment, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - Gifts and Grants, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - Tuition, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 406)
    - Ticket Income, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 407)
  - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 408)
  - Budget Information, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 409)
  - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 410)
  - Budget Yale School of Drama - Repertory Theatre Preparation, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 411)
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 412)
  - Budget, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 413)
  - Yale Budget Operational, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 414)
  - Budget Operation, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 415)
  - Budget Items, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 416)
  - Yale Operating Statement, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 417)
  - Yale School of Drama - YRT Budget Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 418)
  - Budget, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 419)
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 420)
  - Drama School: Cabaret, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 421)
  - Drama School: Summer Cabaret, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 422)
  - Collaborative Workshop: Production Guidelines, undated (Box 9, Folder 423)
  - Acting Department, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 424)
  - Design Department, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 425)
  - Development: Yale School of Drama - YRT Director of Development, Sidney Baker, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 426)
  - Directing Department, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 427)
  - Dramaturgy Internships, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 428)
  - Dramaturgy and Dramatic Criticism Department, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 429)
  - Playwrighting Department, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 430)
  - Playwright Chair Applications, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 431)
  - Technical Design and Production Department, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 433)
  - Technical Design and Production: Ben Sammler: Space Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 434)
  - Stage Management Department, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 435)
  - Theatre Administration Department, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 436)
  - Yale School of Drama: Office of Associate Dean, 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 437)
  - Faculty Appointments and Procedure Correspondence, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 438)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 439)
  - Yale School of Drama: Faculty, Miscellaneous, 1983-1989 (Box 9, Folder 440)
  - Prompter, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 441)
  - Yale School of Drama: Financial Aid, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 442)
  - Pepine - Sammler, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 443)
  - Yale School of Drama: Group Memos, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 444)
  - Yale School of Drama: Library, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 445)
  - Yale School of Drama: Registrar, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 446)
  - School Shows, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 447 - 448)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle: Yale School of Drama School Show, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 449)
  - School Shows, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 450)
  - Yale School of Drama: Safety, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 451)
  - Memos and Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 452)
  - Yale School of Drama: Student Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 453 - 454)
  - Yale School of Drama: Thesis Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 455)
  - Security, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 456)
  - Student Casting, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 457)
  - Yale Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 458)
  - Budget Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 459)
  - Yale School of Drama: Yale Drama Alumni Association, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 460)
  - Budget Meetings, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 461)
  - Drama School Budget Review, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 462)
  - To Dean Richards from S. Penney (Box 9, Folder 463)
  - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 464)
  - Budget Preparation, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 465)
  - Budget Preparation, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 466)
  - Othello, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 467)
  - YRT: Rep IV, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 468)
  - Union Boys, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 469)
  - Stitchers and Starlight Talkers, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 470)
  - Crazy from the Heart, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 471)
  - Winterfest, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 472)
  - Rep IV: Walk in the Woods, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 473)
  - Rep V, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 474)
  - Rep VI: Elizabeth, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 475)
  - Rep III: Winter's Tale, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 476)
  - Rep III The Marriage, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 477)
  - Yale Rep, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 478)
  - Production YRT, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 479)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 480)
  - Rep V, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 481)
  - Rep VI, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 482)
  - The Marriage, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 483)
  - Blood Knot, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 484)
  - Blood Knot in New York City, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 485)
  - A Child's Tale, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 486)
  - Winterfest, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 487)
  - Winterfest, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 488 - 489)
  - Yale School of Drama: Magnin, Jeff, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 490)
  - Student Directing Thesis Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 491)
  - Production Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 492)
  - Directors, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 493)
  - Medea, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 495)
  - Lloyd Richards: Personal, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 496)
  - Yale University
    - Affirmative Action, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 497)
    - Afro-American Center, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 498)
    - Afro-American Studies, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 499)
    - Association of Alumni, 1983-1988 (Box 10, Folder 500)
    - Yale Alumni Fund Status Report, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 501)
    - University Committee on Drama, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 502)
    - Office of the Bursar, 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 503)
    - Yale College: Theatre Studies Committee, 1983-1988 (Box 10, Folder 504)
    - Yale College, 1984-1989 (Box 10, Folder 505)
    - Undergraduate Departments, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 506)
    - Residential Colleges (except Morse), 1984-1988 (Box 10, Folder 507)
    - Morse College, 1983-1988 (Box 10, Folder 508)
    - Office of the Dean of Yale College, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 509)
    - Committee Teaching Residential Colleges, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 510)
  - Council Priorities and Planning, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 511)
  - Deans of Arts: Music, Drama, Art, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 512)
  - Yale Dramat, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 513)
  - Department of English, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 514)
  - General Council and Director of Government Relations, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 515)
  - Literary Properties Committee: Office of the General Council, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 516)
  - Strike Local 34, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 517)
  - Graduate and Professional Student, 1984-1988 (Box 11, Folder 518)
  - Yale Grievance Procedure, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 519 - 520)
  - Yale University Director Grant and Contract Administration, 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 521)
  - Yale University Grounds and Maintenance, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 522)
  - Yale University Human Resources, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 523)
  - Yale University Office of Institutional Research, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 524)
  - Yale University Library, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 525)
  - Yale University: Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 526)
  - Yale University, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 527)
  - Yale Management, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 528)
  - Yale University Finance and Administration, 1983-1988 (Box 11, Folder 529)
  - Office of Foundation Relations, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 530)
  - President Designate Schmidt, 1985-1988 (Box 11, Folder 531)
  - Yale University Office of the President, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 532)
  - President's Advisory Committee, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 533)
  - H. Broude, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 534)
  - Literary Properties Comm, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 535)
  - Committee on Non-traditional Forms of Education, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 536)
  - Presidential Committee for Hewlett Quadrangle, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 537)
  - Committee on Racial and Ethnic Harassment, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 538)
  - Office of Provost, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 539)
  - Yale University Office of the Provost, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 540)
  - Office of the Associate Provost, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 541)
  - Yale University Office of the Secretary, 1975-1987 (Box 11, Folder 542)
  - Office of Development and Alumni Affairs, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 543)
  - Office of Vice President for Finance and Administration, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 544)
  - Yale University Personnel Department, 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 545)
  - Yale School of Art, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 546)
  - Yale School of Divinity, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 547)
  - Yale Law School, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 548)
  - Yale School of Music, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 549)
  - Yale School of Organization and Management, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 550)
  - Yale University Union Drive, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 551)
  - Yale University Whitney Humanities Center, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 552)
  - Yale Club of New Haven, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 553)
  - Yale Press, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 554)
  - Recommendations for Guggenheim, 1979-1985 (Box 11, Folder 555)
  - Recommendations for MacArthur, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 556)
  - Information on Lloyd Richards, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 557)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts: Awards, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 558)
  - Lloyd Richards: Awards, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 559)
  - Lloyd Richards May '82 Speech, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 560)
  - Convocation, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 561)
  - Lloyd Richards: Invitations, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 562)
  - LR's Speech to Congregation Emanuel, undated (Box 11, Folder 563)
  - Wayne State University, 1980-1987 (Box 11, Folder 564)
  - Richards, L. Personal, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 565)
  - Wayne State University (Box 11, Folder 566)
  - Richards: Finances, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 567)
  - Lloyd Richards, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 568)
  - Lloyd Richards Old Receipts, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 569)
  - Duse, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 570)
  - Sarcophagus, undated (Box 12, Folder 571)
  - Moon over Miami, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 572 - 573)
  - Women and Water, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 574)
  - Miscellaneous Filing, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 575)
  - Openings, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 576)
  - Convocation Speech, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 577)
  - Convocation, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 578)
  - The Road to Mecca: Program, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 579)
  - Naked, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 580)
  - Cobb, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 581)
  - First draft: Playboy of the West Indies, undated (Box 12, Folder 582)
  - Playboy of the West Indies, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 583)
  - Piano for Sale, 1982-1986 (Box 12, Folder 584)
  - The Piano Lesson, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 585)
  - Fences: Production Aspects, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 586)
  - The Piano Lesson, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 587 - 588)
  - A Walk in the Woods, undated (Box 12, Folder 589)
  - The Cemetery Club, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 590)
  - Apocalyptic Butterflies, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 591)
  - The Miser, undated (Box 12, Folder 592)
  - Exact Change, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 593)
  - Intermezzo, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 594)
  - Wild Oats or the Strolling Gentlemen, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 595)
  - Student Productions, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 596)
  - Yale School of Drama Class Schedule, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 597)
  - Schedules, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 598)
  - Incoming Class, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 599)
  - Students, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 600)
  - Winterfest, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 601)
  - Winterfest Seminars, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 602)
  - Winterfest Readings, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 603)
  - Neapolitan Ghosts, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 604)
  - Winter's Tale, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 605)
  - A Walk in the Woods, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 606)
  - Elizabeth, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 607)
  - A Place with the Pigs, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 608)
  - Electra, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 609)
  - Becoming Legends: Joan Casa deMont, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 610)
  - School II True Blue and Trembling, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 611)
  - Drama 50's, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 612)
  - Measure for Measure, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 613)
  - Drama 50's, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 614)
  - Rep. I Heartbreak House, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 615)
  - Old Contact Sheets, 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 616)
  - Blood Knot, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 617)
  - Rep. I Blood Knot, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 618)
  - Blood Knot: Philadelphia, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 619)
  - Rep. II Neapolitan Ghosts, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 620)
  - Little Eyolf, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 621 - 623)
  - Ma Rainy Press Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 624 - 625)
  - Broadway Ma Rainy, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 626)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 627 - 629)
  - Yale: paid expense reimbursement requests, 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 630)
  - Non-Yale: paid expense reimbursement requests, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 631 - 632)
  - Travel Expenses, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 633)
  - Yale Expense Forms, 1981-1986 (Box 13, Folder 634)
  - Richards: Dinner - Benefit, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 635)
  - Lloyd Richards: Reimbursement and Expenses, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 636)
  - LR Diary Expense Pages, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 637)